until a short video about STS or live
直到有关STS的简短视频或直播
but handsome highlights and hobbies I
但我很帅气的亮点和爱好
have a problem my app right and in
我的应用程式有问题
orders request my thing that my own
订单要求我自己的东西
research service returns empty results
研究服务返回空结果
so I found the owner's request mapping
所以我找到了所有者的请求映射
and I can verify that with the life hint
我可以通过生活提示来验证
that I have here right
我在这里正确
so it's a green box life answer
所以这是一个绿色盒子生活的答案
highlights are green boxes around mainly
亮点主要是绿色框
annotations in your source code so those
源代码中的注释
are usually the places where beans are
通常是豆子所在的地方
defined for it in orange Athens so if we
为它定义在橙色的雅典，所以如果我们
hover on the slide request mapping rates
将鼠标悬停在幻灯片请求映射率上
actually that exact if it has a life it
实际上，如果它有生命的话
was URL some when you build the
当您建立网址时
process from where the sequester mapping
从隔离器映射的过程
has been accepted fun so let's get back
已经被接受的乐趣，让我们回到
to the problem so the problems were the
问题的原因是
only research service so let's navigate
仅研究服务，让我们浏览
to is the condition and I can see that
条件是，我可以看到
it's being wired into we have the satyr
它被连接到我们有色狼
but let's hover on now let's see how
但现在我们将鼠标悬停
this live information can help us so
这些实时信息可以帮助我们
we're now around the controller right so
我们现在在控制器周围，所以
we can see all the beans that are being
我们可以看到所有的豆子
worked in or where the stuff was being
在工作或工作地点
injected into so since it's a controller
注入，因为它是一个控制器
being it's not getting injected into
被没有注入
anything right but we can see there are
没事，但我们可以看到
beans that work into it so this arrow
豆工作，所以这个箭头
left means that beans are being wired in
左边表示正在连接Bean
and I can see that there is older boys
我看到有个大男孩
doing an empty on the research service
在研究服务上做空
being worried and so there's more
担心，所以还有更多
detailed information about it or there
关于它的详细信息
is an ambien ad type and resource if
是一种环境广告类型和资源，如果
resources available and you know our
可用资源，您知道我们的
controller bean ID and again some
控制器bean ID，再来一些
process information so we could see that
处理信息，以便我们可以看到
there is automatic annotation so that's
有自动注释，所以
where empty owner search service is
空的所有者搜索服务在哪里
being worked into this controller we
在这个控制器中工作
could also see a highlight over the
也可以看到
constructor here for the only repository
唯一存储库的构造函数
right so there is no other why it's
对，所以没有别的原因了
annotation but for components
注释，但用于组件
constructors with parameters have
具有参数的构造函数具有
parameters as implicitly Otto wired
参数作为隐式Otto连线
beans so that's why only repositories
豆，所以这就是为什么只有存储库
they were in BIM right so let's go back
他们是正确的BIM，所以我们回去
to our other words you can see that I
换句话说，你可以看到我
have to hover on on a highlight to get
必须悬停在亮点上才能获得
the information so if it's too annoying
信息，如果太烦人了
you could turn on cold lands preference
你可以打开寒冷的土地偏好
right and that will show you some little
对，那会告诉你一些
summary of what the hover is going to be
悬停的摘要
about so for beans that gives us in
对于使我们进入
beans that are being alter wired in this
在此更改连线的咖啡豆
beam and where this bean is being
梁和这个豆子在哪里
injected into right so for all the words
注入正确的所有单词
we will only get beans that are injected
我们只会得到注入的豆子
into it right so let's let me get to the
正确，所以让我进入
type of this empty search service and we
此空搜索服务的类型，我们
could see that you know the type kind of
可以看到您知道类型
has expected of mutation right it just
期待突变吧
returns an actual list but if we
返回实际列表，但是如果我们
navigate to the resource where this bean
导航到该bean所在的资源
is defined that what might be more
被定义为可能更多
interesting right so this is where it's
有趣的权利，这就是它的所在
defined with this MP notation we can see
用这个MP符号定义，我们可以看到
that there is a beam that's being wired
有一束正在接线的光束
and which is all the repository right
这是所有存储库的权利
and there is a bean where this only
还有一个豆子
research service is being injected into
研究服务正在注入
which is all the controller we just have
这就是我们所拥有的所有控制器
a right here from right so we could see
从右边在这里，这样我们就可以看到
there is an F right and if he searches
有F权利，如果他搜索
false FG under search service is
搜索服务下的FG虚假为
returned as only search service right so
作为唯一的搜索服务返回，所以
let's see why proper kiss is search is
让我们看看为什么正确的吻是搜索
false so it's coming from properties
错误，因此它来自属性
which is a game and all to where I've
这是一个游戏，我一直都在
been
是
so let's not get to its type because
所以我们不要进入它的类型，因为
something in might going with the type
可能与类型有关
right and we can see this configuration
正确，我们可以看到此配置
properties I mean so there's a pet
属性，我的意思是，有一只宠物
clinic owners profits so pet clinic
诊所老板获利，所以宠物诊所
owners searches externalized property by
所有者通过以下方式搜索外部财产
default false right so let's try and fix
默认的错误权限，让我们尝试修复
this property in the application yellow
应用程序中此属性为黄色
file
文件
so it's that clinic clinic own research
所以这是诊所自己的研究
sorry truth so now ideally our beam
对不起真相，所以现在最好是我们的光束
should be the right be about empty
应该是正确的关于空
search service beam butts the old
搜索服务束屁股老
research service and yes we can see that
研究服务，是的，我们可以看到
has been restarted with dev tools and
已使用开发工具重新启动，并且
now we see that its owner search service
现在我们看到它的所有者搜索服务
being word end so that fixes our problem
成为单词结尾，以解决我们的问题
so this information this highlights code
因此，此信息突出显示了代码
Lance's information about life beans is
兰斯有关生活豆的信息是
also available in vs codes the opener vs
也可以在vs代码中使用揭幕战vs
code we could see the same code Lance's
代码我们可以看到Lance的相同代码
right and same highlights in our source
正确和我们的资料来源中的重点
code so we hover on the controller we
代码，因此我们将鼠标悬停在控制器上
could see the same report about being
可以看到相同的报告
beans being wired and you could also
豆被连线，您也可以
navigate to you know in this case to the
在这种情况下导航到您知道的
resource where the beam is defined which
定义波束的资源
is here you see the same information
在这里，您会看到相同的信息
exactly the same so you could also click
完全一样，因此您也可以单击
on this request mapping like request
在这个请求上映射像请求
mapping URL and it will take you in the
映射网址，它将带您进入
browser to this URL so that's that's a
浏览器访问此URL，因此
that's a quick overview of STS for a
这是STS的快速概述
like put highlights ants and harvests
像放亮蚂蚁和收获
for you thank you for watching
为你谢谢你的收看
you
您